It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
We now return
to How I Met Your Father.
Oh, Barney, I'm never going to
meet the right girl and get married.
You know, Ted,
don't you think it's kind of strange
for a guy in his 20s to always be talking
about getting married,
rather than getting laid?
- Barney, I'm in love with you.
- Suit up!
All right, come on, everyone.
Go get dressed. It's ballet night.
Lois, don't freaking put me
through this again.
Peter, a little culture is
good for this family.
Besides, you liked The Nutcracker,
didn't you?
No, Lois, I did not.
The Nutcracker had zero physical comedy.
And with a name like The Nutcracker,
I thought,
"Oh, this'll be worth a few yucks. "
But, no, Lois, that title wrote a check
that those queers on stage
refused to cash.
Peter, we're going.
Well, we're not the first people
to be dragged off against our will.
- Are we there yet?
- No!
- Damn it, I swear to God,
I will turn this ship around!
- That works.
- Okay.
- Lf you want to teach us a lesson...
- Yeah, that's even better.
All right, if that's what you...
Wait a minute!
You know, Meg, female ballet dancers
are famous for anorexia and bulimia and...
It seems to work out for them.
So... Hintedy-hint-hint.
Boy, this is gonna be long.
So, you kids develop
any good pot connections
- at your school yet?
- What?
- Yeah.
- Lois, we'll be right back.
Meg's gonna take me outside to poop.
Hello?
- Hey, Quagmire.
- Hey, Peter, what's up?
- I'm stuck at the stupid ballet.
- Get out of here. You serious?
- Yeah.
- So am I!
- What?
Yeah, I got dragged here
by this broad I'm trying to screw.
Where you sitting?
Look across
at the other balcony,
I can see you.
Oh, my God! What do we do?
What do we do?
What do we do? We're both here.
Oh, my God, we should text each other.
Hang up! Hang up!
Chris, how many times have I told you,
no reading during meals.
I have a history test today, Mom,
and I couldn't study last night
because you made us go to the ballet.
Yeah, right in her ass.
Well, Chris, you're not gonna learn
any history from this.
- This textbook is from 1896.
- What?
- "Chapter Three. Here Comes Utah. "
- Let me see that.
"Negroes, America's Dancingest
Rapefolk. " That's awful!
We don't use the word "negro" anymore.
What the hell?
Are these schools so underfunded
that they can't afford textbooks
from this century?
Well, I am gonna raise hell about this
at the next PTA meeting.
Well, let me know if you need help.
I can be very persuasive.
I gave the next speech
after the Braveheart guy.
They can take our lives,
but they can never take our freedom!
And, and, let's not forget the tax
they levied on properties
that are in abutment of church lands.
So, yeah! Let's do it!
All right, let's get this meeting underway.
For our first order of business,
we'll go to Bruce.
Oh, hey, y'all said my name!
Welcome to our meeting
here at the school.
We've got lots
of exciting topics here tonight.
We gonna have a puppet show,
we gonna have some jazz.
No, I'm just kidding.
We have some business
to take care of, though.
I'm sorry I pulled y'alls legs.
I'm just a little excited
'cause I met somebody today.
Someone in the bookstore.
Someone who likes
the same kind of literature as I do.
Oh, and the adventure begins again.
Excuse me, Principal Shepherd,
there's something I'd like to discuss.
The school has gone too far
with these budget cuts.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Griffin,
but the "No Child Left Behind" law
cost us our federal funding
because our students' test scores
were too low.
They cut a school's funding
if it's got low test scores?
This is not what the founding fathers
had in mind.
Okay, we're here to sign this declaration
of our independence.
Let's take roll call first.
- Thomas Jefferson?
Here.
- Benjamin Franklin?
- John Footpenis?
It's Hancock now.
Why?
Mind your business,
that's why.
Well, somehow this school needs
to raise its test scores right away!
I suppose there is one thing I can do
to raise the school's test average.
Then do it!
All right.
We'll drop the dumbest student we have.
Chris Griffin is hereby expelled.
But if I leave now, I won't hear
who's the dumbest kid in the school.
Cool, I don't have to go to school.
I can just pee in my bed all day.
Chris, being expelled is a serious thing.
Peter, we've got to find another school
for him.
I say, I could home-school him.
After all, I taught Cleveland
how to make Jiffy Pop.
Oh!
So, do you think
your school would be right for Chris?
Oh, absolutely.
Quahog School for the Deaf
has great programs,
both academic and athletic.
In fact, you're just in time
for our homecoming pep rally.
- What are we gonna do to Lincoln?
Kill them!
- I can't hear you!
Let's just go.
Welcome to
the Quahog Maritime School, Chris.
Our curriculum consists of being on boats
for long periods of time with men.
Just men. For many days at a time.
Up on the deck with lots of men,
or down in the galley with lots of men.
Is this some kind of pirate school?
Well, a certain kind of pirate.
Yes, we've been called that.
- I don't know.
- Is there some kind of pre-school program?
You know, I have to admit,
I've always been a little worried
about Chris,
but I guess I just convinced myself
things would work out for him.
But with no education,
what kind of future can he possibly have?
Well, what are we supposed to do, Lois?
I mean, it's not like the high school
will take him back.
And every other school we've tried
just doesn't... Oh, crap!
My son got into DeVry.
Oh, good, what'd he have to do,
open the door?
Can't you let me have anything?
Wait, wait, wait. Hang on, hang on.
What are we fighting about?
- You know, I have completely forgotten.
- Me, too.
Something about a coupon?
- I cannot for the life of me remember.
- Oh, my God, that's ridiculous.
You know what,
I just... I hope I didn't hurt you
- because I'd feel terrible about that.
- No, no, no. I'm all right.
But, listen, you know what,
let me make it up to you.
Why don't you let my wife and I
take you out to dinner.
Well, that sounds lovely.
That was delicious.
You know, I drive by this place all the time
and I've never been inside,
isn't that funny?
Yeah, you know,
Nicole and I came here by accident.
We had reservations at another place
and they...
- Right, right, honey?
- Yeah. They couldn't seat us
for, like, an hour,
so we ended up coming here
- and we just loved it.
- Loved it.
I can see why. I mean, that halibut was...
That may have been the best halibut
I've ever had.
Well, I'm glad we talked you out
of the pork chops, huh?
Yes! Thank you!
Oh, oh, let me, let me, let... I'll get that.
I'll get that.
- Oh, no, no, no, no. I got it.
- No, no, no, no, no. I'm taking care of this.
No, no, no, your money's no good here.
No, my food was more expensive.
I feel bad if...
We invited you. I've got this.
- Look, just let go of the check.
- You let go of the check.
- I'm not taking my hand off this thing.
- Well, neither am I.
Let go of the check.
- Ernie, if he wants to...
- Stay out of this!
Don't you talk to my wife like that!
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do about it?
Sorry.
And every other school we've tried
just doesn't seem to be a good fit
for Chris.
Well, there is one other option.
Daddy, there's something I need you
to do for me.
Chris got expelled
from James Woods High,
and, well, I was wondering
if you could get him
into that fancy boarding school
you went to.
You want me to get Chris
into Morningwood Academy?
It would mean so much to our family.
All right, I'll pull some strings
on one condition.
I want Peter
to do something really humiliating.
Well, what did you have in mind?
He has to shoot and star
in a shot-for-shot remake of Liar Liar
for my amusement.
Do you know why I stopped you?
I didn't fasten my seat belt,
I didn't look in my rear view mirror,
I didn't signal when I pulled away
from the curb,
I almost hit a Chevy,
I changed lanes in the intersection
without signaling, I changed lanes
while running a red light and speeding.
- Well, Chris, here we are.
- Wow, this school is really nice.
Boy, a degree from here would set you up
with any job you wanted.
Yes, I should attend this institution.
Perhaps one day I could be more powerful
than King Friday.
I am the supreme ruler
of the Neighborhood of Make-Believe.
All will kneel before...
What kind of freaking king lives
next to the train tracks?
What is this, Mexico?
- Hi, is this Room 214?
- Oh, you must be our new dorm-mate!
I'm Rogers ChapStick,
heir to the ChapStick fortune.
And this is Virgil MasterCard,
heir to the MasterCard fortune.
Oh, yes, yes,
how do you do, sir?
And this is James Bottomtooth IV.
- I'm Chris.
- Let me get those bags for you. Johann?
Um...
Oh, dear. Johann tells me your luggage
is the luggage of the poor.
Well, I am poor.
Oh. Oh, I see.
What the...
Ow! Ow! Ow!
- This school is not for your kind!
- Why?
I still don't fully understand!
And that was the third time
I slept with Katherine Harris.
Well, I love her politics,
but how is she in bed?
Well, as anyone in Florida will tell you,
she knows how to rig an erection.
One time I picked my nose
and I swear
I could feel the bottom of my eye.
- Shut up, poor kid.
- No, I'm serious, look!
- So, Chris, how's the new school?
- It's awful! I hate it!
Everybody's mean to me
because I'm not rich.
Oh, no, Chris, that's horrible.
All right, look, I'll tell you what.
I'll call Daddy and I'll see
if there's anything he can do.
Good, 'cause I haven't been this miserable
since I had to throw Rocky Balboa
out of the Shamrock Meat Company.
Look, I'm sorry, I can't have you in here
punching the meat.
I mean, there's really not too many things
you can't do in here,
but that is one of them.
What about Paulie?
He's having sex with the meat.
- Hey, Rock, I'm porking it.
- That's a good one.
Phew!
Well, that's enough fun for one day.
I'm sweating more
than a non-legacy applying to Yale.
Where am I?
Grandpa? What are you doing here?
Chris, welcome
to the Skull and Bones Society.
This is where the most powerful men
in the world are groomed for their futures.
Every president, every CEO,
every douche bag named Ryan Seacrest.
The Skull and Bones Society
has been a part of my family for decades,
and we want you to become a member.
- Really? Wow, cool!
- Excellent.
You get your own stock portfolio,
a percentage of the 9/11 Victims Fund,
and the best medical care on the planet.
You'll be kept as healthy as a horse.
- So, how's that leg doing?
- Great! Great! Never better!
Good. Why don't you try
putting some weight on it?
Oh, sure.
Yes! Yes! Oh, that's good!
That feels good! Very strong!
Sorry, Thunder, I got to put you down.
How's your leg? Huh? How's your leg?
You ready to race? Huh?
We now return to
Japanese Girls Think
Small Versions of Things Are Really Cute.
Oh!
Look at my tiny dog!
I'm gonna put it in my tiny purse!
Tiny phone! Tiny everything!
Peter, have you seen this tuition bill?
Morningwood Academy
is charging us $30,000.
Well, looks like we're all gonna have
to take second jobs.
I guess I'll see if I can get my old gig back,
selling buttscratchers at the ballpark.
Buttscratcher! Buttscratcher!
Get your buttscratcher here!
- Buttscratcher!
- Buttscratcher?
- Buttscratcher.
Buttscratcher.
Buttscratcher!
- Buttscratcher!
Chris, come here, you'll love this.
The first Thursday of every month
we go to a local orphanage,
pick out a kid, fill out all the paperwork,
and then don't take him home.
- It's hilarious.
- That sounds kind of cruel.
No, no, you'll love it. It's great.
Come on! Come on in!
Your family's waiting in here!
There are toys and a puppy!
And food that's not served
from warming trays!
Come on! You got to want it!
Oh, you got to do better than that!
Okay, I guess you don't want a new family,
toys and a puppy.
Hi, everybody, I'm home!
- Hi, Chris.
- Hey, how are you?
Well, tell us everything, sweetie.
How's school going so far?
It's great, Mom!
I got powerful connections now,
thanks to Grandpa.
Chris, I'd give you a hug,
but I'm exhausted from working two jobs
to pay your tuition.
I've been selling buttscratchers.
- Buttscratcher!
- No, Peter.
- Peter, no!
- Buttscratcher!
- No!
- Buttscratcher.
- Dad, you...
You got an extra job
just to put me through school?
We all did, Chris.
Meg and I have been working nights.
I'll take the one on the right!
Well, once again, Meg,
I'll be back in an hour.
And I got a job
following fat people around with a tuba.
Stop it! Cut it out!
I have a glandular problem!
That'll be $60.
- You wanted to see me, Grandpa?
- Yes, Chris. Your pledge period is over.
The Skull and Bones elders are now
ready to admit you to our ranks.
As is customary
with all our new members,
you now have to spend seven minutes
in the closet
with our most senior member.
We don't start the clock
until the door closes.
You know, Grandpa,
I don't think I wanna go through with it.
We all had to do it, Chris.
Now get in there.
No, I mean,
I think I wanna go back to my old school.
My family's working so hard
to pay my tuition here, and I feel bad.
Is there any way you can get me
back into James Woods High?
Well, I suppose I could pull some strings,
if that's really what you want, Chris.
- It is.
- All right, consider it done.
Thanks, Grandpa.
- Sorry, Master Herbert.
- Sorry?
You better get your ass
in that closet, Pewterschmidt.
Yes, sir.
I am so tired of you.
It's good to have you back, buddy.
Thanks, Dad.
I didn't really fit in there anyway.
The rooms were only 15 by 20.
If I didn't learn to laugh at myself,
I'd be dead right now.
Why don't you take your stuff
up to your room, Chris?
Okay, Mom.
Cut it out! I'm just trying to live my life!
No one taught me about carbs!
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru